KSHITIJ SAXENA









PROFILE

Fueled by the ambition to build things bigger and better, I specialize in developing Windows and Web apps using .NET but do not limit myself to one technology. With proven communication, teamwork, leadership skills and 'can do' attitude, will be a valuable addition to a good team.

SKILLS

C# SQL .NET Core **MERN Stack REST API** Communication Problem Solving Teamwork Adaptability Leadership

MORE INFO









EXPERIENCE

Since 2021

SSE - ALSOENERGY - GURUGRAM

Working as a part of API team to deliver requirements specified by the Product team.

2018 - 2021

SSE - ACCENTURE - GURUGRAM

Working as a .NET developer to develop, test and deliver the requirements specified by a large reinsurance client. Currently handling applications based on tech stacks such as Winforms, WPF, ASP.Net, MERN and Xamarin Forms.

Major accomplishments:

- Received Rising Star award for creating extraordinary value for client.
- Received Accenture APEX award for demonstrating ownership and originating opportunities for business growth.
- Suggested and delivered several innovations for client applications.
- Consistently recognized by the client and peers for the quality of solutions provided.

2017 - 2018

SDE – SEDEMAC MECHATRONICS - PUNE

Worked as a part of the Off-Highway Engines team to develop and maintain the Windows Applications for flashing and configuring Generator Control Units (GCUs).

2015 - 2017 | **SE** - TATA CONSULTANCY SERVICES - PUNE

EDUCATION

2014

B. TECH - INDERPRASTHA ENGINEERING COLLEGE

Completed with an aggregate of 64.8%. Developed a micro controller-based Timer Switch as project with the team and filed a patent for the same.

2008/2010 10TH/12TH GRADE - KENDRIYA VIDYALAYA

Cleared with an aggregate of 85.6% and 82.3% respectively.

INTERESTS



WRITING **JOURNALS**



COOKING



VIDEO GAMING



READING



SINGING